supernovaox.com 2015-04-26

# Super Nova OX

OUR NEW NEWS LETTER EMAL ADDRESS IS news@.supernovaox.biz please make it free of spam filter  
Due to massive demand for more payment processor options, we are extending time to begin the 1st cycler phase.  
" Upgrade membership " and " Daily Surf Earning " is now open.  
Earn 2 cents for each site surfed! Max daily surf = 25 sites  
_Total return for membership = 120% (12$) and upgrade in 40$ FIVEDOLLARFUNNEL balance_

Upgraded members also receive advertising credits  
Website(surfing) Credits  1,000 \- Banner Credits 1,000 \- Textad Credits 5,000

New surf plan added- 1% daily total 120% return  
Surf 5 Website(s) Daily to Earn  
Website(surfing) Credits  1,000 \- Banner Credits 2,000 \- Textad Credits 5,000

### **SUPERNOVAOX PRIVACY POLICY**

**~What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site,  or fill out a form. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address and phone number. You may however visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
*To personalize your experience  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs

*To improve our website  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

*To improve customer service  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs

*To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the service requested.

*To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.  
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  
Transactions are only completed through processor accounts where the only information stored is your username or email (depending on the processor used).

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  
We use cookies to help us remember, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. Our website and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
